angiesdiary.com 2011-12-21

# Privacy Policy | Angie's DIARY

_**This privacy statement covers Angie’s DIARY. Please read this statement carefully before proceeding to access Angie’s DIARY. Your use of Angie’s DIARY indicates your agreement to abide by the Terms in effect.**_

 **Information Collection**  
Angie’s DIARY is the sole owner of the information collected on the Angie’s DIARY. Angie’s DIARY may collect information from our users at several different points on the Angie’s DIARY.

**Comments**  
In order to enhance their use of the Angie’s DIARY, users can choose to leave comments on particular articles of interest. To leave a comment, users must submit information including a valid email address. Angie’s DIARY uses this information to screen out users who leave comments prohibited by our terms and conditions of use, and will not pass this information to any other organization.

**Cookies  
**By setting a cookie, users will not have to log in with a password more than once, thereby saving time while on the site’s discussion board. We store a cookie on each user’s machine that contains a username and encrypted password. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use Angie’s DIARY products or services that require you to “sign in,” and you may not be able to take full advantage of all offerings. However, not all Angie’s DIARY services require that you accept cookies.

**Third Party Cookies**  
Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, Angie’s DIARY has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Angie’s DIARY only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

 **Third Party Advertising**  
The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by Google, among other services. Information about users’ visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not username, date of birth, or any other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site. For more information about Google and cookies, please click here.

 **Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

 **Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, Angie’s DIARY may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on Angie’s DIARY.

 **Business Transitions**  
In the event Angie’s DIARY goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

 **Links**  
The Angie’s DIARY contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Angie’s DIARY is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Angie’s DIARY.

 **Notification of Changes**  
Whenever Angie’s DIARY changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

 **Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or notices of violations to these terms and conditions, please contact the editor of the Angie’s DIARY at contact@angiesdiary.com  

#### Related Posts on Angie's DIARY:

  * No Related Posts
